Southern New England Telephone Company Records
© 2005 University of Connecticut
- Series III: Corporate Relations, undated, 1915-1995
  - Advertising
    - Residence
      - Residence Reference Information, 1980 (Box 223:, Folder 2084)
    - Samples
      - 1924-1929 (Box 223:, Folder 2085)
      - 1926 (Box 223:, Folder 2086-87)
      - 1927 (Box 223:, Folder 2088-89)
      - 1928 (Box 223:, Folder 2090)
      - 1928 (Box 224:, Folder 2091)
      - 1929 (Box 224:, Folder 2092-93)
      - 1930 (Box 224:, Folder 2094-96)
      - 1931 (Box 224:, Folder 2097-98)
    - Samples (OS), note; see boxes: 248-255, folders 2099-2150
    - Sample Advertisements (OS) [large binders by year 1955-1980], note: see box/volume 256-285
    - Sample Marketing Aids, 1987 (Box 224:, Folder 2151)
    - Sample Printed Material for Clients
      - #1, 1986 (Box 224:, Folder 2152)
      - #2, 1986 (Box 224:, Folder 2153)
      - #3, 1987 January (Box 224:, Folder 2154)
      - #4, 1987 January (Box 224:, Folder 2155)
      - #5, 1987 January (Box 224:, Folder 2156)
      - #6, 1987 February (Box 224:, Folder 2157)
      - #7, 1987 March (Box 224:, Folder 2158)
      - #8, 1987 March (Box 224:, Folder 2159)
      - #9, 1987 April (Box 224:, Folder 2160)
      - #10, 1987 April (Box 224:, Folder 2161)
      - #11, 1987 May (Box 224:, Folder 2162)
      - #12, 1987 May (Box 224:, Folder 2163)
      - #13, 1987 June (Box 224:, Folder 2164)
      - #14, 1987 July (Box 224:, Folder 2165)
      - #15, 1987 August (Box 224:, Folder 2166)
      - #16, 1987 August (Box 224:, Folder 2167)
      - #17, 1987 September (Box 224:, Folder 2168)
      - #18, 1987 October (Box 224:, Folder 2169)
      - #19, 1987 October (Box 224:, Folder 2170)
      - #20, 1987 December (Box 224:, Folder 2171)
      - #21, 1988 January (Box 224:, Folder 2172)
      - #22, 1988 February (Box 224:, Folder 2173)
      - #23 [1988?] (Box 224:, Folder 2174)
      - #24, 1988 April (Box 224:, Folder 2175)
      - #25, 1988 June (Box 224:, Folder 2176)
      - #26, 1988 July (Box 224:, Folder 2177)
    - Samples, Year In Review, 1988 (Box 225:, Folder 2178-79)
    - Schedules, 1980 (Box 225:, Folder 2180)
    - Schedules, 1981 (Box 225:, Folder 2181)
    - Schedules, 1982 (Box 225:, Folder 2182)
    - Schedules, ATT, 1982 (Box 225:, Folder 2183)
    - Schedules, Bell System, 1980 (Box 225:, Folder 2184)
    - Schedules, Television, 1979-1980 (Box 225:, Folder 2185)
    - Services Promotions, 1980s (Box 225:, Folder 2186)
    - Sports
      - CIAC Basketball, 1970 (Box 225:, Folder 2188)
      - Fall Sports Package, NFL and UCONN Football, 1972 (Box 225:, Folder 2189)
      - Sports Package, 1972-1973 (Box 225:, Folder 2190)
      - Sports Package, 1974 (Box 225:, Folder 2191)
      - UCONN Basketball and UP With People Program, 1968-1969 (Box 225:, Folder 2192)
      - UCONN Basketball, 1966-1967 (Box 225:, Folder 2193)
      - UCONN Basketball, 1968-1969 (Box 225:, Folder 2194)
      - UCONN Basketball, 1969-1970 (Box 225:, Folder 2195)
      - UCONN Basketball and Football, 1971-1974 (Box 225:, Folder 2196)
      - UCONN Football, 1975 (Box 225:, Folder 2197)
      - Yellow Page and Sports Packages, 1972 (Box 225:, Folder 2198)
    - Spot Franchise
      - 1968 (Box 225:, Folder 2199)
      - 1969-1970 (Box 225:, Folder 2200)
      - 1970 (Box 225:, Folder 2201)
      - 1971 (Box 225:, Folder 2202)
      - 1972 (Box 225:, Folder 2203)
      - 1973 (Box 225:, Folder 2204)
      - 1974 (Box 225:, Folder 2205)
      - 1975 (Box 225:, Folder 2206)
      - 1976 (Box 225:, Folder 2207)
      - 1977 (Box 225:, Folder 2208)
    - Spot Franchise Charts, 1968-1973 (Box 225:, Folder 2209)
    - Sprint Information, 1980 (Box 225:, Folder 2210)
    - Tracking Surveys, 1970-1976 (Box 225:, Folder 2213)
    - Yearly Summaries, Bell System, 1965-1971 (Box 225:, Folder 2214)
    - Yearly Summary Comparisons, 1965-1971 (Box 225:, Folder 2215)
    - Yearly Summary
      - 1971 (Box 225:, Folder 2216)
      - 1972 (Box 225:, Folder 2217)
      - 1973 (Box 226:, Folder 2218)
      - 1974 (Box 226:, Folder 2219)
      - 1975 (Box 226:, Folder 2220)
      - 1976 (Box 226:, Folder 2221)
      - 1977 (Box 226:, Folder 2222)
      - 1978 (Box 226:, Folder 2223)
      - 1979 (Box 226:, Folder 2224)
      - 1980 (Box 226:, Folder 2225)
    - Yellow Pages, 1978 (Box 226:, Folder 2227)
    - Yellow Pages, 1979 (Box 226:, Folder 2228)
    - Yellow Pages, 1980 (Box 226:, Folder 2229)
    - Yellow Pages, 1981 (Box 226:, Folder 2230)
    - Yellow Page Ads, 1979 (Box 226:, Folder 2231)
    - Yellow Pages and ATT, 1981 (Box 226:, Folder 2232)
    - Yellow Pages ATT/SNET, 1979-1980 (Box 226:, Folder 2233)
    - Yellow Pages and ATT/SNET, 1981-1982 (Box 226:, Folder 2234)
    - Yellow Pages Budget, 1981 (Box 226:, Folder 2235)
    - Yellow Pages Budget, 1982 (Box 226:, Folder 2236)
    - Yellow Pages Business To Business, 1978 (Box 226:, Folder 2238)
    - Yellow Pages Business To Business, 1979 (Box 226:, Folder 2239)
    - Yellow Pages Business To Business, 1980 (Box 226:, Folder 2240)
    - Yellow Pages, Business To Business, 1981 (Box 226:, Folder 2241)
    - Yellow Pages, Business To Business, 1981 (Box 226:, Folder 2242)
    - Yellow Pages, Business To Business, 1982 (Box 226:, Folder 2243)
    - Yellow Pages Business To Business Categorization, 1979 (Box 226:, Folder 2244)
    - Yellow Pages, Business To Business Direct Marketing, 1982 (Box 226:, Folder 2245)
    - Yellow Pages, Business To Business Inserts, 1982 (Box 226:, Folder 2246)
    - Yellow Pages Business To Business Plans, 1980 (Box 226:, Folder 2247)
    - Yellow Pages, Business To Business Radio, 1981 (Box 226:, Folder 2248)
    - Yellow Pages, Business To Business Research, 1979 (Box 226:, Folder 2249)
    - Yellow Pages, Business To Business Special Projects, 1981 (Box 226:, Folder 2250)
    - Yellow Pages Business To Business Study, 1979 (Box 226:, Folder 2251)
    - Yellow Pages Community Campaign, 1978 (Box 226:, Folder 2252)
    - Yellow Page Coupons, 1980 (Box 226:, Folder 2253)
    - Yellow Pages Dentist Campaign, 1980 (Box 226:, Folder 2254)
    - Yellow Pages Lawsuit, 1979 (Box 226:, Folder 2255)
    - Yellow Pages Lawsuit, 1982 (Box 226:, Folder 2256)
    - Yellow Pages Long Range View, 1981-1982 (Box 226:, Folder 2257)
    - Yellow Pages National Association, 1982 (Box 226:, Folder 2258)
    - Yellow Pages Presentation, 1973 (Box 226:, Folder 2259)
    - Yellow Pages Promotional Program, 1981 (Box 226:, Folder 2260)
    - Yellow Pages Promotions and Studies, 1976 (Box 544:, Folder 2261)
    - Yellow Pages Radio Campaign, 1980 (Box 544:, Folder 2262)
    - Yellow Pages Red Campaign, 1978-1979 (Box 544:, Folder 2263)
    - Yellow Pages Red Campaign, 1980 (Box 544:, Folder 2264)
    - Yellow Pages Red Campaign, 1980 (Box 544:, Folder 2265)
    - Yellow Pages/Red Direct Marketing, 1979 (Box 544:, Folder 2266)
    - Yellow Pages Reference and Research Materials, 1979 (Box 544:, Folder 2267)
    - Yellow Pages Research, 1976-1980 (Box 544:, Folder 2268)
    - Yellow Pages Schedule, 1980 (Box 544:, Folder 2270)
    - Yellow Pages Study, 1973 (Box 544:, Folder 2271)
    - Yellow Pages Study, 1974 (Box 544:, Folder 2272)
    - Yellow Pages Study, 1976 (Box 544:, Folder 2273)
    - Yellow Pages Studies, 1977 (Box 544:, Folder 2274)
    - Yellow Pages Trumbull Campaign, 1980 (Box 544:, Folder 2278)
    - Yellow Pages Usage Study, 1977 (Box 544:, Folder 2279)
    - Yellow Pages Usage Study, CT, 1977 (Box 544:, Folder 2280)
    - Yellow Pages Usage Study, 1978 (Box 544:, Folder 2281)
    - Yellow Pages Usage Studies, 1981 (Box 544:, Folder 2282)
  - Customer Complaints
    - Customer Comment Guide, 1930 (Box 227:, Folder 2283)
    - to FCC [Federal Communications Commission] (binder), 1949-1969 (Box 227:, Folder 2284)
    - to PUC [Public Utilities Commission] Equipment (binder), 1915-1968 (Box 227:, Folder 2285)
    - to PUC, Rates (binders)
      - 1926-1934 (Box 227:, Folder 2286)
      - 1926-1957 (Box 227:, Folder 2287)
      - 1958-1966 (folder, w/Index) (Box 227:, Folder 2288)
      - 1958-1966 (Box 227:, Folder 2289)
    - 1967-1969 (Box 227:, Folder 2290)
      - 1970 (Box 228:, Folder 2291)
      - 1971 (Box 228:, Folder 2292)
    - to PUC, Service (binders)
      - 1916-1947 (Box 228:, Folder 2293)
      - 1948-1951 (Box 228:, Folder 2294)
      - 1952-1955 (Box 228:, Folder 2295)
      - 1956-1962 (Box 228:, Folder 2296)
      - 1963-1966 (Box 229:, Folder 2297)
      - 1967-1968 (Box 229:, Folder 2298)
      - 1969 (Box 229:, Folder 2299)
      - 1970 (Box 229:, Folder 2300)
      - 1971 (Box 229:, Folder 2301)
  - Employee Information
    - Anniversary Card, Church St. Building, 1988 (Box 230:, Folder 2303)
    - Company Structure, 1970 (Box 230:, Folder 2320)
    - Consumer Health Skills Leader's Guide, 1982 (Box 230:, Folder 2323)
    - CT Finest Magazine, 1988 (Box 230:, Folder 2325)
    - Ecology Program, 1977 (Box 230:, Folder 2327)
    - Ecology Program, 1980 (Box 230:, Folder 2328)
    - Ecology Program Reports, 1970s-1980s (Box 230:, Folder 2329)
    - Ecology Program Report, 1981 July (Box 230:, Folder 2330)
    - Ecology Report, 1981 July (Box 230:, Folder 2331)
    - Elevator Cards, 1962-1963 (Box 230:, Folder 2332)
    - Elevator Cards, 1965 (Box 230:, Folder 2333)
    - Elevator Cards (OS), note: see box 286-287 (large binders)
    - Health Promotion Manual, 1982 (Box 230:, Folder 2341)
    - Health Promotion Manual and Guide, 1982 November (Box 230:, Folder 2342)
    - Keep It Off Program, undated (Box 230:, Folder 2353)
    - Labor/Management Agreement, 1968 September (Box 230:, Folder 2355)
    - License Contract Study, 1979 (Box 230:, Folder 2356)
    - Management Topics, 1982 (Box 230:, Folder 2361)
    - News Briefs, 1976 (Box 230:, Folder 2363)
    - Pamphlets, Company Services, 1990s (Box 230:, Folder 2367)
    - Pamphlets, Financial Facts, 1974 (Box 230:, Folder 2368)
    - President Carter's Ecology Package, 1977 (Box 230:, Folder 2370)
    - Privacy of Records Policy, 1980 (Box 230:, Folder 2372)
    - Program Samples, 1980 (Box 230:, Folder 2374)
    - Rate Case Background Information Booklet, 1982 March (Box 230:, Folder 2379)
    - Rate Case Backgrounder Program, 1982 (Box 230:, Folder 2380)
    - Rate Case Backgrounder Program, Part I, 1982 (Box 230:, Folder 2381)
    - Rate Case Backgrounder Program, Part II, 1982 (Box 230:, Folder 2382)
    - Rate Request Booklet, 1980 (Box 230:, Folder 2383)
    - Safety Cards
      - 1935 January - November (Box 230:, Folder 2392)
      - 1936 (Box 230:, Folder 2393)
      - 1937 (Box 230:, Folder 2394)
      - 1938 (Box 230:, Folder 2395)
      - 1939 (Box 230:, Folder 2396)
      - 1940 (Box 230:, Folder 2397)
      - 1941 (Box 230:, Folder 2398)
      - 1942 (Box 230:, Folder 2399)
      - 1945 (Box 230:, Folder 2400)
      - 1946 (Box 230:, Folder 2401)
      - 1947 (Box 230:, Folder 2402)
      - 1951 February - March (Box 230:, Folder 2403)
      - 1952 (Box 230:, Folder 2404)
      - 1953 February - December (Box 230:, Folder 2405)
      - 1954 (Box 230:, Folder 2406)
      - 1955 February - October (Box 230:, Folder 2407)
      - 1956 February - December (Box 230:, Folder 2408)
      - 1957 (Box 230:, Folder 2409)
      - 1958 (Box 230:, Folder 2410)
      - 1959 (Box 230:, Folder 2411)
      - 1960 (Box 230:, Folder 2412)
      - 1961 (Box 230:, Folder 2413)
      - 1962 January - February (Box 230:, Folder 2414)
      - 1965 (Box 230:, Folder 2415)
    - Strike Letter, 1968 May (Box 230:, Folder 2424)
  - Jean Handley Files
    - Management Employment Conference, 1976 (Box 230:, Folder 2507)
    - Programs
      - Affirmative Action Program (Vets and Handicapped), 1976 (Box 230:, Folder 2525)
  - Public Information
    - ATT Correspondence
      - 1978 March - July (Box 230:, Folder 2545)
      - 1978 August - December (Box 230:, Folder 2546)
      - 1979 January - May (Box 545:, Folder 2547)
      - 1979 June - December (Box 545:, Folder 2548)
    - Brochures/Magazines/Pamphlets, 1980s (Box 545:, Folder 2550)
    - Buried Cable Booklet, 1968/1991 (Box 545:, Folder 2551)
    - Business Promotions, 1987-1991 (Box 545:, Folder 2552)
    - Centennial Booklet, 1977 (Box 545:, Folder 2565)
    - Centennial Program/History, 1978 (Box 545:, Folder 2566)
    - Centennial Planning, 1977 May (Box 545:, Folder 2567)
    - Corporate Symbol Promotion, 1984 (Box 545:, Folder 2574)
    - Ecology Program Reports, 1974-1980 (Box 545:, Folder 2582)
    - Editorial, Alfred W. Van Sinderen, undated (Box 545:, Folder 2583)
    - Educational Relations, 1980 (Box 545:, Folder 2585)
    - Informational Packages (OS), note: see box 288, folders 2601-2612 (Box 288)
    - Interviews (transcripts of)
      - Aleska, G. and Johnson, J., 1976 (Box 231:, Folder 2613)
      - Burchard and Hyde, 1976 (Box 231:, Folder 2614)
      - Corves, G., 1976 (Box 231:, Folder 2615)
      - D'Onofrio, D., 1976 (Box 231:, Folder 2616)
      - Eckstrom, R., 1977 (Box 231:, Folder 2617)
      - Gradwell, J., 1976 (Box 231:, Folder 2618)
      - Little, R. P., 1976 (Box 231:, Folder 2619)
      - Lombardi, R., 1976 (Box 231:, Folder 2620)
      - Miglio, D., 1976 (Box 231:, Folder 2621)
      - Owens, O. H., 1976 (Box 231:, Folder 2622)
      - Owens, O. H., 1976 (Box 231:, Folder 2623)
      - Tinker, D., 1976 (Box 231:, Folder 2624)
      - Van Sinderen, A., 1977 (Box 231:, Folder 2625)
      - Van Sinderen, A., 1976 (Box 231:, Folder 2626)
      - Zupka, D., 1976 (Box 231:, Folder 2627)
    - I-SNET [Internet], 1994 January (Box 231:, Folder 2628)
    - LINX Promotion [Cellular], 1987 (Box 231:, Folder 2635)
    - Mailing Samples, 1988 (Box 231:, Folder 2636)
    - News Conference, Lightnet, 1985 May - June (Box 231:, Folder 2639)
    - News Conference, Sonecor, 1983 January (Box 231:, Folder 2640)
    - News Releases, 1956-1979 (Box 231:, Folder 2642)
    - News Releases, 1986 (Box 231:, Folder 2643)
    - News Releases, 1987 (Box 231:, Folder 2644)
    - News Releases, 1987-1994 (Box 231:, Folder 2645)
    - News Releases, 1994-1998 (Box 231:, Folder 2646)
    - News Release, Fiber Optics, 1989 December (Box 231:, Folder 2647)
    - News Release, Lease/Finance, 1992 September (Box 231:, Folder 2648)
    - News Report, Yellow Pages, 1976 July (Box 231:, Folder 2650)
    - Pamphlets
      - 1970-1986 (Box 231:, Folder 2651)
      - 1980s (Box 231:, Folder 2652-54)
    - Press Conference, Van Sinderen, 1974 April (Box 231:, Folder 2655)
    - Press Luncheons, Van Sinderen
      - 1974 (Box 231:, Folder 2660-62)
      - 1977 (Box 231:, Folder 2663-64)
    - Promotional Items (OS), note: see box 289, folders 2665-2672 (Box 289)
    - Promotional Items (OS), note: see box 290, folders 2673-2679 (Box 290)
    - Publications, 1980s (Box 231:, Folder 2680)
    - Rate Guide, Part I, 1936 (Box 231:, Folder 2681)
    - Rate Guide, Part II, 1936 (Box 231:, Folder 2682)
    - Road After 1984 Information Package (OS), 1983-1984; note: see box 290 (Box 231:, Folder 2685)
    - Road After 1984 New Release Package (OS), 1983-1984; note: see box 290 (Box 231:, Folder 2687)
    - Samples, 1960s (Box 231:, Folder 2692)
    - Samples, 1980s (Box 231:, Folder 2693)
    - Special Olympics Media Kit (OS), 1995; note: see box 290 (Box 231:, Folder 2699)
    - Special Olympics Program, 1993 (Box 231:, Folder 2700)
    - Special Olympics, 1994 (Box 231:, Folder 2701)
    - Speeches
      - Gustavson, D., 1976 (Box 231:, Folder 2702)
      - Miglio, D., 1984 (Box 231:, Folder 2703-04)
      - Owens, O. H., 1976 (Box 231:, Folder 2705)
      - Owens, O. H., 1977 (Box 231:, Folder 2706)
      - Scully, W. J., 1976 (Box 231:, Folder 2707)
      - Van Sinderen, 1977 January (Box 231:, Folder 2708)
      - 1976 November (Box 231:, Folder 2709)
      - 1976 June (Box 231:, Folder 2710)
      - 1977 April (Box 231:, Folder 2711)
    - Speeches, Indexes, through 1979 (Box 232:, Folder 2712)
      - 1956-1961 (Box 232:, Folder 2713)
      - 1983 November - December (Box 232:, Folder 2714)
      - 1984 January - May (Box 232:, Folder 2715-16)
      - 1984 May - December (Box 232:, Folder 2717-18)
      - 1985 (Box 232:, Folder 2719-20)
      - 1986 (Box 232:, Folder 2721-23)
      - 1987 (Box 233:, Folder 2724-26)
      - 1966-1986 Unidentified (Box 233:, Folder 2727)
      - undated Unidentified (Box 233:, Folder 2728)
      - Brown, Charles L., 1977-1980 (Box 233:, Folder 2729)
      - Brown, Charles L., 1980-1982 (Box 233:, Folder 2730)
      - Handley, Jean M., 1980-1984 (Box 233:, Folder 2731)
      - Handley, Jean M., 1985-1987 (Box 233:, Folder 2732)
      - Monteith, Walter H.
        - 1982-1983 (Box 233:, Folder 2733)
        - 1984-1985 (Box 233:, Folder 2734)
        - 1986-1987 (Box 233:, Folder 2735)
        - 1987 (Box 233:, Folder 2736)
      - Olson, J. E., 1980-1983 (Box 234:, Folder 2737)
      - Van Sinderen, A. W
        - 1966-1967 (Box 234:, Folder 2738)
        - 1968 (Box 234:, Folder 2739)
        - 1972 (Box 234:, Folder 2740)
        - 1977-1978 (Box 234:, Folder 2741)
        - 1980 (Box 234:, Folder 2742)
        - 1980-1981 (Box 234:, Folder 2743)
        - 1982 (Box 234:, Folder 2744)
        - 1983 (Box 234:, Folder 2745)
        - 1984 (Box 234:, Folder 2746)
        - 1984-1985 (Box 234:, Folder 2747)
      - Von Auw, A., 1965, 1968, 1981 (Box 234:, Folder 2748)
    - World's Fair Promotion Binder (OS) (Box 291:, Folder 2749)
  - Oversized
    - Advertising
      - Artwork; (loose materials) Line-Art, Drawings, Transparencies, 1970s-1980s (Box 235)
      - Illustrations, 1950s (Box 236)
      - Illustrations, 1950s-1970s (Box 237)
      - Illustrations
        - George DeCrosta First Century, 1970s (Box 238:, Folder 1988-1998)
        - Directory Centennial Prints, 1970s (Box 238:, Folder 2038)
      - Illustrations; Mike Barber/Yellow Pages, 1950s (Box 239)
        - Bear Hunt (Box 239:, Folder 1999)
        - Mountain Climber (Box 239:, Folder 2000)
        - Scuba Diver (Box 239:, Folder 2001)
        - Fox Hunt (Box 239:, Folder 2002)
        - Deep Sea Fisherman (Box 239:, Folder 2003)
        - Woman Skier (Box 239:, Folder 2004)
        - Big-game Hunter (Box 239:, Folder 2005)
        - Geologist (Box 239:, Folder 2006)
      - Mechanicals, note: also loose materials (Box 240:, Folder 2024-2025,)
      - Mechanicals, 1980s (Box 241)
      - Photographs, undated (Box 242)
      - Photographs, undated (Box 243)
      - Posters, 1960s-1970s (Box 244)
      - Posters, 1970s-1980s (Box 245)
      - Posters (Large Binder), 1970-1972 (Box 246)
      - Printing Plates, undated (Box 247)
        - Business Office Informationals (Box 247:, Folder 2037-2038)
        - Directory Informationals (Box 247:, Folder 2039)
        - Ecology Ad (Box 247:, Folder 2040)
        - Extension Ads (Box 247:, Folder 2041-2045)
        - Long Distance Ads (Box 247:, Folder 2046-2051)
        - Phone Store Informationals (Box 247:, Folder 2052)
        - Total Phone Ads (Box 247:, Folder 2053)
      - Samples
        - Account Review, 1986 (Box 248:, Folder 1843)
        - Business Ads, 1970s-1980s (Box 248:, Folder 2099)
        - Business Ads, Bell System, 1979 (Box 248:, Folder 2100)
        - Business Ads, Posters, 1980s (Box 248:, Folder 2101)
        - Business to Business Yellow Pages Ads, 1980s (Box 248:, Folder 2102)
        - Samples, undated (Box 249:, Folder 2103)
        - Samples Long Distance, 1950s (Box 249:, Folder 2104)
        - Sample Ads ATT, [1970s] (Box 249:, Folder 2105)
        - Sample Ads Bell System, [1970s] (Box 249:, Folder 2106)
        - Sample Ads Western Electric, [1970s] (Box 249:, Folder 2107)
        - Newspaper Ads (Large Poster Board), 1953-1955 (Box 250)
        - Pamphlets, Booklets, Directory and Residence Ads, 1930s (Box 251:, Folder 2108-2124)
        - Rates, Long Distance, Health and Safety (employee ads), 1920s-1930s (Box 252:, Folder 2125-2131)
        - Residence Ads and Mechanicals, 1980s (Box 253:, Folder 2132-2138)
          (also loose materials)
        - Residence, Long Distance and Service Ads, 1936-1940 (Box 254:, Folder 2139-2141)
        - Services, Brochures, Educational and Business Ads, 1980s (Box 255:, Folder 2142-2150)
      - Sample Advertisements, (Large Binders)
        - 1955 (Box 256)
        - 1955 (Box 257)
        - 1956 (Box 258)
        - 1956 (Direct Distance Dialing) (Box 259)
        - 1957 (Box 260)
        - 1958 (Box 261)
        - 1959 (Box 262)
        - 1960 (Box 263)
        - 1961 (Box 264)
        - 1962 (Box 265)
        - 1963 (Box 266)
        - 1964 (Box 267)
        - 1965 (Box 268)
        - 1965 (Box 269)
        - 1966 (Box 270)
        - 1966 (Box 271)
        - 1967 (Box 272)
        - 1968 (Box 273)
        - 1969 (Box 274)
        - 1970 (Flat Box) (Box 275)
        - 1971 (Box 276)
        - 1972 (Box 277)
        - 1973 (Box 278)
        - 1974 (Box 279)
        - 1975 (Box 280)
        - 1976 (Box 281)
        - 1977 (Box 282)
        - 1978 (Box 283)
        - 1979 (Box 284)
        - 1980 (Box 285)
    - Employee Information
      - Elevator Cards, Safety Cards, Posters (large binder), 1962-1963 (Box 286)
      - Elevator Cards, 1965-1966 (Box 287)
    - Public Information
      - Informational Packages
        - All Distance, 1992-1993 (Box 288:, Folder 2601)
        - Centennial Celebration, 1978 January (Box 288:, Folder 2602)
        - Education Program, Phenomenal Phone Book, 1989 (Box 288:, Folder 2603)
        - Industry News, 1980s (Box 288:, Folder 2604)
        - I-SNET, 1994 August (Box 288:, Folder 2605)
        - Links To Learning, 1988 October (Box 288:, Folder 2606)
        - LINX Program, 1985 (Box 288:, Folder 2607)
        - Press Conference Package, NHSO, 1993 May (Box 288:, Folder 2608)
        - Planning and Forecast, 1968 March (Box 288:, Folder 2609)
        - Recruiting, undated (Box 288:, Folder 2610)
        - Sonecor Press Conference Package, 1983 (Box 288:, Folder 2611)
        - Sonecor Packages, 1984-1985 (Box 288:, Folder 2612)
      - Promotional Items
        - Autographed Hand-fan, undated (Box 289:, Folder 2665)
        - Official New Haven Anniversary Commemorative Medal, 1988 (Box 289:, Folder 2666)
        - New Corporate Symbol, undated (Box 289:, Folder 2667)
        - Radio Commercial Record Sample, 1984 (Box 289:, Folder 2668)
        - SNET WATS Wings Pin, undated (Box 289:, Folder 2669)
        - Yellow Pages Note Pad, 1991-1992 (Box 289:, Folder 2670)
        - 771-Call Program, 1991-1992 (Box 289:, Folder 2671)
        - 771-Call Program, 1991-1992 (Box 289:, Folder 2672)
      - Promotional and Informational Items
        - Ecology Program Promotional Item, 1980 (Box 290:, Folder 2673)
        - Ecology Promotion Item, Yellow Pages Dress, 1968 (Box 290:, Folder 2674)
        - Exhibit Handbook, Special Olympics, 1995 (Box 290:, Folder 2675)
        - Holiday Materials, undated (Box 290:, Folder 2676)
        - Lightwave Press Conference Promotional Items, 1979 (Box 290:, Folder 2677)
        - Service Charges Chart, undated (Box 290:, Folder 2678)
        - SNET Classic Tennis, 1994 (Box 290:, Folder 2679)
      - Road After 1984 Information Package, 1983-1984 (Box 290:, Folder 2685)
      - Road After 1984 News Release Package, 1983-1984 (Box 290:, Folder 2687)
      - Special Olympics Media Kit, 1995 (Box 290:, Folder 2699)
      - World's Fair Promotion Binder, 1964-1965 (Box 291:, Folder 2749)
- Series IV: Product Service Development, undated, 1889-1967
  - Appreciation Course for Plant Engineering Headquarters Employees Engaged in Cable and Conduit Record Work, 1942 (Box 292:, Folder 2752)
  - Blueprints and Diagrams (OS), Note: folders 2753-2761
    - Buildings
      - New Haven - Court St., 1904 (Box (cab):, Folder 2753)
      - Stamford - Dial Office, 1928 (Box (cab):, Folder 2754)
      - Stamford - Greyrock Place (25), 1921-1925 (Box (cab):, Folder 2755)